Ok so first things first, leather.
Leather we've already talked about previously in a segment.
Leather is very important and you want to upkeep it very well.
You want to have a color protector before you even apply amazing wipes on it.
Wipes that can help with UV protection.
So if your going to go out in that sun with that bag and look great on that beach you want to be able to have the best protection on as possible.
So if your going to try to protect your bag.
You don't want any discolor in any relative bag.
So you want to open it up somewhere where people normally don't see.
Wipe a little color protector your wipe on there to make sure the bag isn't really dark brown compared to the light brown everywhere else.
You also maybe maybe want some rain protection on every other bag that you have at home or anything else.
Like this bag here or your fabrics.
Fabrics are very important you can also store your bags in the thing that they came in so that you can zip it up save it up and just put it away.
That way its stored, nice and neat bring it out of the bag, still smells fresh.
Its very important.
So up keeping your bag is very important for a long lasting healthy bag.
Up next were going to to talk about different patterns, colors, shapes, sizes of bags